Yexin Mao

Canberra, Australia, 0458045615, u7530987@anu.edu.au

LINKS	Homepage, LinkedIn, Google Scholar	
PROFILE	I have broad interests in machine learning, computer vision. I had experience in machine learning with label noise and self-supervised learning of graph neural networks. My current main research focus is on the neural rendering, especially, neural radiance field. I want to find a balance between academia and industry in my future life.	
EDUCATION		
Mar 2018 — Jun 2022	Bachelor of Advanced Computing, University of Sydney	Sydney
	Advised by Wei Huang, Tongliang Liu	
	First Class Honours	
	Thesis: Bolvar: Bootstrap Your Own Latent with Variance Regularization on Graphs	
Jul 2022	Master of Machine Learning and Computer Vision, Australian National University	Canberra
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
Aug 2018 — Nov 2020	Tutor, HD Education	Sydney
	Tutoi, 112 Education	- 7 7
Jan 2021 — Dec 2021	Intern, Institute of Automation, Chinese Academy of Sciences.	Beijing
	Advised by Zhiwei Liu, Xiangyu Zhu	
	Brief job description: Human key points detection, dataset collection and labelling, initial "Xiao Chu" (Multi-modal-model) etc.	build of platform for
Aug 2021 — Dec 2021	Intern, ObjectEye	Beijing
	Brief job description: Vehicle detection.	
Aug 2022 — Nov 2022	Intern, Wuhan AI Research	Wuhan(Remote)
	Brief job description: Digital human, talking neural head avatar.	
Nov 2022 — Present	Intern, Australian National University	Canberra
	Advised by <u>Huan Lei</u>	
	Brief job description: Controllable neural radiance field	
TEACHING	INFO1110: Introduction to Programming	
	Teaching assistant of Python programming for undergraduate students.	
	COMP3670/COMP6670 - Introduction to Machine Learning	
	Class representative of the Introduction to Machine Learning course for undergraduate students and master students.	
PUBLICATIONS	Cracking enabled unclonability in colloidal crystal patterns authenticated with computer vision. Yuhuan Li, Yexin Mao, Jiahui Wang, Zhiwei Liu, Pan Jia, Na Wu, Haitao Yu, Jinqiao Wang, Yanlin Song, Jinming Zhou. In Nanoscale, 2022.	